AoM Additional Records 6117
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AoM Additional Records
1990-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Academy of Management (AoM)
6117
2.22 cubic feet
2.2 linear ft.
Records.
5806222
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 29, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 28, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5289: AoM Records 5289 MB: AoM Memorabilia 5289 P: AoM Photographs 5289 PUBS: AoM Publications 5593: AoM Records 5593 AV: AoM Audio-Visual Material 5893m: Leonard R. Burgess "Status of Women in Academy of Management" Memoir 5920 AV: AoM Audio-Visual Collection 5977 mf: AoM Additional copy of publications on Microfilm 6019: AoM Eastern Academy of Management Records 6278: David Van Fleet Collection of Academy of Management Records
Professional associations -- United States; Industrial management -- United States; Academy of Management.; Academy of Management --Archives
5806222
- Academy of management black notebook, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Subsections - Election, Fiscal, Dues, Meetings, Induction, Emblems, Records, Attendance, Fellows Division, and Constitution and Changes
- Box of Kodak Professional Photos taken at the 47th Annual Academy of Management Meeting, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Academy Management Bank statements and withdrawals, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Academy of Management checking receipts from Hancock Bank, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Academy of Management Fellow Ballot material, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Academy of Management Fellow Ballot material, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Academy of Management Membership Directory, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  August 1998. Pgs. 1-15 (2 copies)
- Academy of Management Membership Directory., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  August 1997. Pgs. 1-14 (2 copies)
- Material from the Academy of Management Fellows Dean Election, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Travel and lodging information for Academy of Management Annual Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Folder containing material from the Academy of Management Membership Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Letters and E-mail transcripts of the Fellows Membership Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- More miscellaneous material from the Academy of Management Fellows Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Academy of Management Fellows Ballot Material, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Academy of Management Fellows Election Material, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Academy of Management Fellows Election Material, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Academy of Management Fellows Ballot Material, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Academy of Management Fellows Ballot Material, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Eastern Academy of Management - 37th Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  2000 Proceedings -- May 10-13, 2000, Danvers, Ma.
- Eastern Academy of Management - 37th Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)